Guide to the James Marshall Osborn Correspondence
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Box and Folder List, 1960
  - Cholmondeley, Sybil Rachel Betty Cecile (Sassoon) Cholmondeley, Marchioness of, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 279)
    Houghton
  - Charnley, Audrey, 1953-54 (Box 12, Folder 280)
  - Church, Elsie, 1972-75 (Box 12, Folder 281)
    New Haven friend
  - Churchill, Edward S., 1953-76 (Box 12, Folder 282)
  - Citizens' Committee for a Constitutional Convention, 1956-65 (Box 12, Folder 283)
  - Clair, Colin, 1963-70 (Box 12, Folder 284)
    Researcher at BM
  - Clapp, Sarah L. C., 1936-52 (Box 12, Folder 285)
    Tonson
  - Clarendon Press, 1940-67 (Box 12, Folder 286)
  - Clark, Charles E. (and Dorothy), 1965 (Box 12, Folder 287)
    Lady Chatterly's Lover decision, friends
  - Clark, Elias, 1962-76 (Box 12, Folder 288)
    Master, Silliman College
  - William Andrews Clark Memorial Library, 1955-74 (Box 12, Folder 289)
  - Clark, W. D., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 290)
  - Clayton, Thomas S., 1959-76 (Box 12, Folder 291)
    Shakespeare, etc.
  - Cleaver, Mrs. A. H., 1963-65 (Box 12, Folder 292)
    Spence
  - Clemens, J. L., 1942 (Box 12, Folder 293)
  - Clements, Arthur L., 1966-69 (Box 12, Folder 294)
    Traherne
  - Clements, R. C., n.d. (Box 12, Folder 295)
  - Clemoes, Peter A. M., 1965 (Box 12, Folder 296)
    Aelfric fragments
  - Clifden, Francis Gerald Agar-Robartes, 7th Viscount, b. 1883, 1951-52 (Box 12, Folder 297)
  - Clifford, James Lowry, 1901-1978, 1935-41 (Box 13, Folder 298-305)
    Department of English, Columbia University, Mrs. Thrale-Piozzi and Johnson biographer, J. M. Osborn's oldest scholarly friend and one of his closest friends
  - Clifford, James Lowry, 1901-1978, 1941-57 (Box 14, Folder 306-313)
  - Clifford, James Lowry, 1901-1978, 1958-78 (Box 15, Folder 314-322)
  - The Club at Mory's, 1963-73 (Box 16, Folder 323)
  - Cluett, Jack and Amanda, 1943-67 (Box 16, Folder 324)
    Friends
  - Coats, William Russell, 1902-1973, and Elizabeth (Spindler), 1952-76 (Box 16, Folder 325-326)
    Cousins
  - Cobham, Charles John Lyttelton, 10th Viscount, 1909-, 1952-72 (Box 16, Folder 327)
    Hagley Hall
  - Coffin, Catherine, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 328)
  - Coffin, C. M., 1941-42 (Box 16, Folder 329)
    Kenyon College
  - Coghill, N. K., 1934 (Box 16, Folder 330)
  - Coke, Gerald, 1958-76 (Box 16, Folder 331)
    English musical friend
  - Colbeck, Norman, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 332)
  - Colbeck Radford & Co., Ltd., 1938-39 (Box 16, Folder 333)
    Booksellers
  - Cole, A. Colin, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 334)
    College of Arms, Malone
  - Cole, Richard C., 1972 (Box 16, Folder 335)
  - Coleridge, A. H. B., 1959-61 (Box 16, Folder 336)
    Coleridge
  - Coleridge, Jane, 1962-68 (Box 16, Folder 337)
    Friend
  - Coley, William B., 1960-71 (Box 16, Folder 338)
    Wesleyan, Fielding
  - Collins, Rowland L., 1974 (Box 16, Folder 339)
    University of Rochester
  - Collins, William, 1959-64 (Box 16, Folder 340)
  - Columbia University Press, 1940-56 (Box 16, Folder 341-342)
    Dryden book, etc.
  - Commander, John, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 343)
    Mahler
  - Commin, Horace G., 1951-52 (Box 16, Folder 344)
  - Congleton, J. E., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 345)
    Sir Herbert Croft
  - Conley, C. H., 1939-47 (Box 17, Folder 346)
  - Connecticut Academy of Arts & Sciences, 1951 Apr 4 (Box 17, Folder 347)
    J. M. Osborn's membership
  - Connelly, Herbert L., 1940-55 (Box 17, Folder 348)
    Wesleyan University Alumni Council
  - Connely, Willard, 1937-58 (Box 17, Folder 349)
    American University Union, London
  - Consumer Consultant Service, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 350)
  - Conway, William E., 1974-76 (Box 17, Folder 351)
    Clark Library, UCLA
  - Coon, Arthur M., 1941-66 (Box 17, Folder 352)
    Seventeenth Century Newsletter
  - Cooper, Dan, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 353)
    Interior decorator
  - Cooper, Henry Spottiswood Fenimore, Jr. (Box 17, Folder 354)
  - Cooper, Lane, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 355)
  - Cooper-Prichard, A. H., 1935-38 (Box 17, Folder 356)
  - Copeland, Thomas Wellsted, 1907-1979, 1947-56 (Box 17, Folder 357-360)
    Edmund Burke, old friend
  - Copeland, Thomas Wellsted, 1907-1979, 1956-79 (Box 18, Folder 361-365)
  - Corson, James C., 1964 (Box 18, Folder 366)
    University Library, Edinburgh, Dryden
  - Coulter, Francis C., d. 1979, 1949-75 (Box 18, Folder 367)
  - Council Manager, 1949-65 (Box 18, Folder 368-370)
  - Cowan, W. A., 1963 (Box 18, Folder 371)
    University Librarian, Adelaide, Malone and Johnson
  - Cowell, F. Richard, 1966-72 (Box 18, Folder 372)
    Historian
  - Cowie, Alec, 1954-70 (Box 18, Folder 373)
    English Department, Wesleyan
  - Cowler, Rosemary Elizabeth, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 374)
  - Cox, J. Stephens, 1953-63 (Box 18, Folder 375)
  - Craigie, Sir William A., 1936-57 (Box 19, Folder 376)
    Social friend
  - Crane, Ronald S., 1886-1967 and Julia, 1934-76 (Box 19, Folder 377-381)
    University of Chicago, cousin, scholar, mentor
  - Crane, Theodore Rawson, 1947-76 (Box 19, Folder 382)
    University of Denver, historian, cousin (son of Verner)
  - Crane, Verner Winslow, d. 1974 and Margaret, 1937-75 (Box 19, Folder 383)
    University of Michigan, historian, cousin
  - Cranfield, Thomas, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 384)
  - Cranmer-Byng, J. L., 1960-62 (Box 19, Folder 385)
    Macartney
  - Crary, J. Noyes, 1942-66 (Box 19, Folder 386)
    War Council
  - Craster, Sir Edmund, 1937-57 (Box 19, Folder 387)
    Bodley's Librarian, Luttrell
  - Crawford, David Alexander Robert Lindsay, 28th Earl of, 1900-197? (Box 19, Folder 388)
  - Creed, Robert P., 1968 (Box 19, Folder 389)
    English Inst.
  - Creel, George, d. 1953, 1940-48 (Box 19, Folder 390)
    Cousin, writer
  - Crewe, Lord, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 391)
  - Crist, Timothy John, 1951-, 1971-75 (Box 19, Folder 392)
    Osborn Collection
  - Croft, Peter J., 1958-76 (Box 20, Folder 393-398)
    MS Department, Sotheby's
  - Croft-Murray, Edward, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 399)
    Prints and drawings, BM
  - Cromer, George Rowland Stanley Baring, 3rd Earl of, 1918-, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 400)
    Ambassador to United States
  - Cronin, Grover, Jr., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 401)
    Burney
  - Crook, Arthur, 1964-73 (Box 20, Folder 402)
    The Times Literary Supplement
  - Cross, Claire, 1957-59 (Box 20, Folder 403)
  - Crow, John, 1957-65 (Box 20, Folder 404)
    Scholar
  - Crum, Margaret C., 1966-76 (Box 20, Folder 405)
    First-Line Index of MS Poetry, Bodleian
  - Crump, Galbraith, 1957-64 (Box 20, Folder 406)
  - Crutchley, Brooke, 1975-76 (Box 20, Folder 407)
    Munby Fellowship
  - Culler, A. Dwight, 1973-75 (Box 20, Folder 408)
    English Department, Yale
  - Cullimore, D., 1954 (Box 20, Folder 409)
  - Culot, Paul, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 410)
  - Cumming, Elmer, 1954-55 (Box 20, Folder 411)
  - Curtis, Arthur, 1934-54 (Box 20, Folder 412)
    Old friend
  - Curtis, Lewis P., 1961-68 (Box 20, Folder 413)
    History Department, Yale, Sterne
  - Curtiss, Samuel, 1933-36 (Box 20, Folder 414)
    African missionary
  - Daiches, David, 1935-73 (Box 21, Folder 415)
    Oxford friend, scholar
  - Dandridge, Edmund P., Jr., 1953-54 (Box 21, Folder 416)
  - Daniel, Robert, 1947-63 (Box 21, Folder 417)
    Kenyon
  - Danielson, Bors, 1957-59 (Box 21, Folder 418)
  - Darwin, K., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 419)
  - David, Elizabeth, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 420)
    Cookbook writer
  - David, G., 1963 (Box 21, Folder 421)
  - Davies, Godfrey, 1950-56 (Box 21, Folder 422)
    Huntington
  - Davies, H. W., 1938-39 (Box 21, Folder 423)
  - Davies, William T., 1935-37 (Box 21, Folder 424)
    Balliol College, Oxford
  - Davin, Daniel Marcus, 1913-, 1949-68 (Box 21, Folder 425-431)
    Clarendon Press, Oxford
  - Davin, Daniel Marcus, 1913-, 1968-76 (Box 22, Folder 432-433)
  - Davin, Winifred Kathleen (Gonley), 1957-62 (Box 22, Folder 434)
    Joyce Cary Papers
  - Davis, Arthur Kyle, Jr., 1966 (Box 22, Folder 435)
    Matthew Arnold
  - Davis, Bertram H., 1960 (Box 22, Folder 436)
    Sir John Hawkins
  - Davis, C. Rexford, 1955-56 (Box 22, Folder 437)
    William Cobbett
  - Davis, Edward H., 1879-1976, 1942-76 (Box 22, Folder 438)
  - Davis, Herbert, 1938-71 (Box 22, Folder 439)
    Cornell
  - Davis, Tom R., 1969-75 (Box 22, Folder 440)
    J. M. Osborn's research assistant, 1969-71, University of Birmingham
  - Davis & Orioli, 1939-54 (Box 22, Folder 441)
  - Dawson, Giles E., 1939-68 (Box 22, Folder 442-444)
    Folger
  - Dawson's Book Shop (Los Angeles), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 445)
  - Dawson's of Pall Mall, 1960-62 (Box 22, Folder 446)
  - Day, Cynes L., 1941-48 (Box 22, Folder 447)
    English Institute
  - Day's Library, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 448)
  - Dearing, Vinton, 1952-62 (Box 22, Folder 449)
  - de Beer, Esmond Samuel, 1895-, 1938-76 (Box 23, Folder 450-454)
    Oxford, Evelyn, Locke
  - Deelman, Christian F., 1961 (Box 23, Folder 455)
    Garrick
  - De Graaf, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 456)
  - de la Grange, Henri-Louis, Baron, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 457)
  - Delio and Montgomery, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 458)
    Mahler, Das klagende Lied copyright
  - De L'Isle, 1970-74 (Box 23, Folder 459)
    Languet portrait for Sidney book
  - de Luca, Giulia (Signora Giuseppe), 1953-59 (Box 23, Folder 460)
    Music, Italy
  - de Mandach, Andre, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 461)
    Sir Martin Mar-All
  - Develin, Joseph, 1936-40 (Box 23, Folder 462)
    American Oxford friend
  - Dewees, Merle, 1951-65 (Box 23, Folder 463)
    New Haven Taxpayers Research Council
  - Dewhurst, Kenneth, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 464)
    Locke letter
  - de Wit, John, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 465)
    Ashmolean, Burney portrait
  - Dick, Hugh, 1959-70 (Box 23, Folder 466)
    UCLA, Sidney, etc.
  - Diether, Jack, 1968-76 (Box 23, Folder 467)
  - Dilworth, J. Richardson, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 468)
    Search for Yale president
  - Dixon, Ross I., Jr., 1954-74 (Box 23, Folder 469)
    City government, etc.
  - Dixon, Peter, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 470)
  - Dobbie, Elliot Von Kirk, 1939-42 (Box 23, Folder 471)
    Columbia, Work in Progress, etc.
  - Dobell, Percy John, 1871-1956, 1936-56 (Box 24, Folder 472-481)
  - Dobell, Robert John, d. 1972, 1956-72 (Box 25, Folder 482-491)
  - Percy Dobell & Son, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 492-498)
    Bills only
  - Percy Dobell & Son, 1938-57 (Box 27, Folder 499-505)
    Bills and customs declarations
  - Dodd, Alan, 1946-49 (Box 28, Folder 506)
    Recommendation for Yale graduate
  - Dollard, Mark, 1964-65 (Box 28, Folder 507)
  - Donner, Henry, 1966-70 (Box 28, Folder 508)
  - Donno, Elizabeth Story, 1965-74 (Box 28, Folder 509)
  - Doubleday, F. N., 1961-63 (Box 28, Folder 510)
    Editor, The New Rambler
  - Douglas, Althea, 1963-73 (Box 28, Folder 511)
  - Douie, Vera, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 512)
    Fawcett Library appeal
  - Dowdeswell, A. G., 1961-69 (Box 28, Folder 513)
    Johnson Society
  - Downer, Alan S., d. 1970, 1949-70 (Box 28, Folder 514-515)
  - Dring, Edward M., 1969-74 (Box 28, Folder 516)
    Quaritch, booksellers
  - Driscoll, Emily, 1948-68 (Box 28, Folder 517-520)
  - Dugdale, Grant, 1964-71 (Box 28, Folder 521)
    Brown University Press
  - Dulau & Co., Ltd., 1938-39 (Box 28, Folder 522)
  - Dulwich College Library, 1936-73 (Box 28, Folder 523)
  - Duncan-Jones, Katherine, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 524)
    Somerville College, Oxford, Sidney
  - Dunham, William H., 1958-62 (Box 28, Folder 525)
    Master of Jonathan Edwards College
  - Dunlop, William, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 526)
  - Dunn, Waldo H., 1965-69 (Box 28, Folder 527)
  - du Pont, Henry F. and Pierre S., 1947-66 (Box 28, Folder 528)
    Cattle breeding, Burke
  - Dutcher, George M., 1937 (Box 28, Folder 529)
    Wesleyan professor
  - Dutton, E. P. & Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 28, Folder 530)
  - Dwyer, Hugh L. and Martha, 1973-76 (Box 28, Folder 531)
    J. M. Osborn's doctor; daughter's visit to Oxford
  - Eade, J. C., 1968 (Box 29, Folder 532)
    Australian National University, Dryden
  - Earle, Anne W., 1957 (Box 29, Folder 533)
  - Eaton, Peter, Ltd., 1961-64 (Box 29, Folder 534)
  - Eaves, T. C. Duncan, 1963-71 (Box 29, Folder 535)
    Richardson, University of Arkansas
  - Eckhardt, Tibor and Ellen, 1943-69 (Box 29, Folder 536)
    Hungarian friends
  - Eddy, Donald D., 1962-71 (Box 29, Folder 537)
  - Edel, Leon, 1966-67 (Box 29, Folder 538)
    Henry James
  - Edgecumbe, John, 1966-76 (Box 29, Folder 539)
    Johnson, etc.
  - Edwards, Francis, Ltd., 1937-66 (Box 29, Folder 540)
  - Edwards, H. W., Ltd., 1951-66 (Box 29, Folder 541)
  - Ehrenpreis, Irvin, 1956-68 (Box 29, Folder 542)
    University of Virginia, Swift
  - Elderton, Sir William, 1959-61 (Box 29, Folder 543)
    Elderton
  - Eldredge, Frances (Mrs. Seneca D.), 1941-70 (Box 29, Folder 544)
  - Eldredge, Harrison, 1959-74 (Box 29, Folder 545)
    Recommendation for graduate school in English, young friend
  - Eliot, Valerie (Mrs. T. S.), 1967-76 (Box 29, Folder 546)
  - Elias, Archibald Cameron, Jr., 1969-76 (Box 29, Folder 547)
    Swift, Temple, etc.
  - Elizabethan Club, 1940-64 (Box 29, Folder 548)
  - Ellinger, Esther Parker, 1940 Sep 15 (Box 29, Folder 549)
    Chatterton
  - Elliot, Jabez, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 550)
  - Ellis, Frank, 1962-74 (Box 29, Folder 551)
    Smith College, 18th century
  - Ellmann, Richard, 1961-73 (Box 29, Folder 552)
    Oxford, Joyce
  - Elton, G. R., 1965-73 (Box 29, Folder 553)
    Cambridge, Whythorne, Sidney
  - Emery, John P., 1939-43 (Box 29, Folder 554)
    Ohio University, Arthur Murphy
  - Emery, Ruth, 1964-76 (Box 29, Folder 555)
    More, Sidney
  - England, Martha W., 1952-76 (Box 29, Folder 556)
    Garrick, Sidney, etc.
  - The English Institute, 1947-76 (Box 29, Folder 557)
  - English-Speaking Union, 1966-67 (Box 29, Folder 558)
  - Erdman, David V., 1956-73 (Box 29, Folder 559)
  - Erskine, David H., 1964-69 (Box 29, Folder 560)
  - Esler, Lemist, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 561)
  - Evans, Carol, 1969-76 (Box 29, Folder 562)
    Bibliography
  - Eversole, Richard, 1972 Feb 8 (Box 29, Folder 563)
    Recommendation for Folger grant
  - Fabbri, Remo, Jr. and Nancy (Rash), 1974-76 (Box 30, Folder 564)
  - Fairchild, Hoxie Neale, 1928-72 (Box 30, Folder 565)
    Columbia
  - Fairer, David, 1971-76 (Box 30, Folder 566)
    Oxford, Warton
  - Falconer, Alexander, 1960-73 (Box 30, Folder 567)
    St. Andrews
  - Farmer, David, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 568)
    University of Texas
  - Faust, Clarence, 1951-59 (Box 30, Folder 569)
    Stanford
  - Feil, J. P., 1958 (Box 30, Folder 570)
    Cornell, Sir Tobie Matthew
  - Fellows, Otis, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 571)
  - Fenner, A. F., Jr., 1951 (Box 30, Folder 572)
  - Fermoy, Ruth Sylvia (Gill), Baroness, 1962-70 (Box 30, Folder 573)
  - Ferrari, Guy, O. S. B., 1961 (Box 30, Folder 574)
    Vatican library
  - Fifer, Charles N., 1953-75 (Box 30, Folder 575)
    Langton
  - Firpo, Massimo, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 576)
  - Fisher, Avery, 1971-72 (Box 30, Folder 577)
    Equipment at Historical Sound Recordings
  - Fisher, John Hurt, 1964-71 (Box 30, Folder 578)
  - Fitzgerald, Robert P., 1961-64 (Box 30, Folder 579)
    Lowth
  - Fleeman, John David, d. 1994, 1962-76 (Box 30, Folder 580)
    Pembroke College, Oxford, Johnson
  - Fleming, John F., 1961 (Box 30, Folder 581)
  - Fleming, Lionel and Hope, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 582)
    Malone and Reynolds research
  - Fletcher, Alick, 1954-62 (Box 30, Folder 583)
  - Fletcher, Harris, 1945-61 (Box 30, Folder 584)
    Clayton
  - Fletcher, Ifan Kyrle (C. & I. K. Fletcher Ltd.), 1939-69 (Box 30, Folder 585-589)
  - Flint, Richard and Margaret, 1942-44 (Box 31, Folder 590)
    Yale friends
  - Florida Press, University of, 1962-67 (Box 31, Folder 591)
    Dryden 2nd edition
  - Folger Shakespeare Library, 1939-69 (Box 31, Folder 592)
  - Fortin, Philip F., 1956-57 (Box 31, Folder 593)
  - Foster, Elizabeth (Read), 1962-76 (Box 31, Folder 594)
    Bryn Mawr College, Braye MSS
  - Foster, Frances, 1964-66 (Box 31, Folder 595)
    Fasciculus Morum
  - Fox, Levi, 1961-62 (Box 31, Folder 596)
    Shakespeare's Birthplace
  - Foxon, David Fairweather, 1923-, 1961-71 (Box 31, Folder 597)
    Oxford, English verse
  - Francis, Sir Francis Chalton, 1901-, 1940-76 (Box 31, Folder 598)
    British Museum
  - Fredericke, Robin, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 599)
    Fanny Burney portrait
  - Freedman, Morris, 1961-62 (Box 31, Folder 600)
  - Freeman, Arthur, 1970-71 (Box 31, Folder 601)
  - Freeman, Eric, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 602)
    John Jones CPB
  - Freese, Winifred, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 603)
    Huntington Library Quarterly
  - French, J. Milton, 1942-62 (Box 31, Folder 604-606)
    Rutgers, Seventeenth Century Newsletter
  - Frick Art Reference Library, 1942-63 (Box 31, Folder 607)
  - Friedman, Arthur, 1941-72 (Box 31, Folder 608)
    Chicago, Modern Philosophy
  - Frost, William, 1965-73 (Box 31, Folder 609)
    Santa Barbara
  - Fry, Mary Isabel, 1949-76 (Box 31, Folder 610)
  - Frye, Northrop, 1950-51 (Box 31, Folder 611)
    MLA, English Inst.
  - Fulton, John F., d. 1960 and Lucia, 1944-63 (Box 31, Folder 612)
    Yale Medical Library, friends
  - Fussell, Paul, Jr., 1964-67 (Box 31, Folder 613)
    Rutgers, English Inst.
  - Gabriner, Paul, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 614)
    Hebrew University, Pope
  - Gaillard, Edward P., 1940-57 (Box 32, Folder 615)
    Stocks, calligraphy
  - Gal, Istvan, 1969-72 (Box 32, Folder 616)
  - Gallaudet, Herbert D., 1942 (Box 32, Folder 617)
  - Gallup, Donald Clifford, 1913-, 1948-63 (Box 32, Folder 618)
  - Gamble, Philip L., 1948-67 (Box 32, Folder 619)
  - Gardner, Dame Helen Louise, 1908-, 1957-76 (Box 32, Folder 620-621)
  - Gardner, William Bradford, 1938-70 (Box 32, Folder 622)
    George Hickes
  - Gassner, John, 1954-66 (Box 32, Folder 623)
    Drama
  - Gfroerer, Herbert, 1962 Feb 9 (Box 32, Folder 624)
    Churchill and Sound Scriber
  - Giacomini, Lynwood, 1952-55 (Box 32, Folder 625)
  - Gibson, Strickland, 1936-68 (Box 32, Folder 626-628)
    Librarian, Bodleian Library
  - Gilbertson, Richard, 1962-66 (Box 32, Folder 629)
  - Gilchrist, Donald B., 1939-74 (Box 32, Folder 630)
    Rush Rhees Library, University of Rochester
  - Gilmer, Jessie A., 1969-72 (Box 32, Folder 631)
    Malone and Reed
  - Gimbel, Richard, 1954-65 (Box 32, Folder 632)
    Yale Library, Curator of Aeronautical Literature
  - Goldschmidt, Lucien, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 633)
    Scope and Contents note
  - Goldwater, Robert, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 634)
  - Goodenough, Erwin R., 1959-62 (Box 33, Folder 635)
    Yale historian
  - Goodspeed's Book Shop, Inc., 1939-68 (Box 33, Folder 636-638)
  - Gordon, Douglas H., 1968 (Box 33, Folder 639)
    William Force Stead
  - Gordon, John D., 1940-74 (Box 33, Folder 640)
    Berg Collection, NYPL
  - Gossett, William Thomas and Elizabeth (Hughes), 1935-75 (Box 33, Folder 641-643)
  - Gost, William F., 1941-58 (Box 33, Folder 644)
    Guaranty Trust Co. of New York
  - Gove, Philip, 1941-62 (Box 33, Folder 645)
    NYU
  - Graduates Club, 1940-70 (Box 33, Folder 646)
  - Graham, Thomas, 1955-56 (Box 33, Folder 647)
  - Graham, Walter, 1935-52 (Box 33, Folder 648)
    University of Illinois, Addison
  - Grant, Douglas, 1921-1969, 1953-69 (Box 33, Folder 649-650)
    Leeds, American literature, 18th century
  - Gray, James, 1954-75 (Box 33, Folder 651)
    Dalhousue University, Johnson
  - Greenberg, Herbert, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 652)
    Advice to a young man on going to Oxford
  - Greene, Donald, 1954-76 (Box 34, Folder 653)
    UCLA, Johnson
  - Greene, James and Elizabeth (Rollins), 1949-69 (Box 34, Folder 654)
    Friends in Pasadena
  - Greene, Richard Leighton, 1904-, 1939-76 (Box 34, Folder 655-657)
    Rochester and Wesleyan, English carol
  - Greer, Rowan A., III, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 658)
    Yale Divinity School
  - Greg, Sir Walter Wilson, 1875-1959, 1937-61 (Box 34, Folder 659)
  - Griffith, R. H., 1940-51 (Box 34, Folder 660)
    University of Texas, Pope
  - Griggs, Earl Leslie, 1959-65 (Box 34, Folder 661)
  - Grimsditch, Herbert B., 1934-38 (Box 34, Folder 662)
    Researcher for J. M. Osborn
  - Griswold, Harlan H., 1961-76 (Box 34, Folder 663)
  - The Grolier Club, 1939-75 (Box 34, Folder 664)
  - Gross, Sarah Chokla, 1940-48 (Box 34, Folder 665)
    Theater Library Association
  - Grover, Karen, 1970-74 (Box 34, Folder 666)
    Henry Colman
  - Groves, James, 1952-55 (Box 34, Folder 667)
    Editor, New Haven Journal Courier
  - Guerlac, Henry, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 668)
  - Haas, Otto, 1957 Aug 30 (Box 35, Folder 669)
  - Habenicht, Rudolph, 1958-61 (Box 35, Folder 670)
  - Haden, H. Jack, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 671)
    Johnson
  - Hagstrum, Jean H., 1952-76 (Box 35, Folder 672)
    Northwestern University, Johnson
  - Haight, Gordon S., 1941-76 (Box 35, Folder 673)
    Yale, George Eliot
  - Hake, Sir Henry M., 1937-52 (Box 35, Folder 674)
    National Portrait Gallery
  - Haldane, J. B. S., 1936-37 (Box 35, Folder 675)
    University of London
  - Hall, A. H., 1959 (Box 35, Folder 676)
  - Hall, Marshall, Jr. and Sally, 1971-76 (Box 35, Folder 677)
  - Hall, Sir Noel, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 678)
    Brasenose College, Oxford
  - Hall, Ridgeway M., 1964-65 (Box 35, Folder 679)
  - Haller, William, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 680)
  - Halliday, Bernard, 1938-60 (Box 35, Folder 681)
  - Halliday, Edward, 1971-73 (Box 35, Folder 682)
    The Club
  - Hallward, Bertrand L., 1952 (Box 35, Folder 683)
    Nottingham University
  - Halsband, Robert, 1914-, 1949-75 (Box 35, Folder 684-689)
    Lady Mary Wortley Montagu, Lord Harvey
  - Halsey, Ralph W., Jr., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 690)
    New Haven Symphony Finance Committee
  - Hamill, Alfred E., 1941 (Box 35, Folder 691)
    Johnson medallion
  - Hamill, Frances, 1956-62 (Box 35, Folder 692)
  - Hamilton, A. C., 1952-75 (Box 35, Folder 693)
  - Hamilton, Charles, 1954-64 (Box 35, Folder 694)
  - Hamilton, F. W. Guy, 1967-76 (Box 35, Folder 695-696)
    The Athenaeum
  - Hamilton, George Heard, 1954-69 (Box 35, Folder 697)
    Friend of Tinker
  - Hamilton, Stella, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 698)
    Friend of Dan Cooper, mother of Elizabeth David
  - Hammond, Anthony D., 1968-75 (Box 36, Folder 699)
    McMaster University, Langbaine, Shakespeare
  - Hanley, Edwin, 1954-60 (Box 36, Folder 700)
    Scarlatti
  - Hannas, T. & L., 1960-68 (Box 36, Folder 701)
  - Hanson, Henry, Jr., 1939-40 (Box 36, Folder 702)
    Student of J. M. Osborn's at Wesleyan
  - Hanson, Lars W., 1953-65 (Box 36, Folder 703)
    Keeper of printed books, Bodleian
  - Hanson, Thomas W., 1963 (Box 36, Folder 704)
    Stanley and Edward's family, father of Lars
  - Harbage, Alfred, 1936-45 (Box 36, Folder 705)
    Penn, Harvard, Shakespeare
  - Hardacre, P. H., 1964 (Box 36, Folder 706)
    Edward Hyde
  - Harding, Walter M. H., 1963-68 (Box 36, Folder 707)
    Collector, donor to American Friends of the Bodleian
  - Hardy, John P., 1961-72 (Box 36, Folder 708-709)
    Johnson, Toronto, University of N. E. (Australia)
  - Harlan, J. Lee, Jr., 1938-39 (Box 36, Folder 710)
    Payne Collier
  - Harman, Roland N., 1937-38 (Box 36, Folder 711)
    Scott
  - Harmon, Cosme, 1974-75 (Box 36, Folder 712)
  - Harmon, Maurice, 1966-67 (Box 36, Folder 713)
    University Review (Dublin)
  - Harris, Brice, 1941-69 (Box 36, Folder 714)
    Arizona State, Dryden
  - Hart, Edward L., 1957-68 (Box 36, Folder 715)
    John Nichols
  - Hart-Davis, Rupert, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 716)
    Hannah More
  - Harth, Philip, 1968-76 (Box 36, Folder 717)
    Wisconsin, 18th century
  - Harvard Library, 1936-68 (Box 36, Folder 718)
  - Harvard University Press, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 719)
  - Harvey-Wood, Harry and Family, 1958-76 (Box 36, Folder 720)
  - Hastings, Robert Pusey, 1973-76 (Box 36, Folder 721)
    Lawyer, Churchill collector
  - Havens, Raymond Dexter, 1941-42 (Box 36, Folder 722)
    Johns Hopkins, Modern Language Notes
  - Hawkins, Harriett, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 723)
    Vassar
  - Hayward, John Davy, 1905-1965, 1954-65 (Box 36, Folder 724-725)